{
    "subject": "resource/First_Light_Division,_Maryland_Volunteers",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableCommander",
    "object": "resource/George_H._Steuart_(militia_general)",
    "human_readable": "The First Light Division, Maryland Volunteers was commanded by George H. Steuart (militia general).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.986155092716217,
            "question": "Who commanded the First Light Division of the Maryland Volunteers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8327776193618774,
            "question": "What information can be gathered about George H. Steuart's leadership style based on his command of the First Light Division?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7424575686454773,
            "question": "What state was the First Light Division associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.653309166431427,
            "question": "What was George H. Steuart's role in the military?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6503557562828064,
            "question": "What were the primary responsibilities of a militia general like George H. Steuart?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.645093560218811,
            "question": "What type of military unit was the First Light Division?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5680460929870605,
            "question": "During what historical period did George H. Steuart serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5615164637565613,
            "question": "To which unit did George H. Steuart belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.446492999792099,
            "question": "Were there any notable achievements or contributions made by the First Light Division?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3646521270275116,
            "question": "Can you name any significant battles or events involving the First Light Division?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The First Light Division, Maryland Volunteers was commanded by George H. Steuart (militia general).",
            "html": "dbpedia_7368_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable achievements or contributions made by the First Light Division?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7368_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which unit did George H. Steuart belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7368_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=During what historical period did George H. Steuart serve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7368_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7368_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"The First Light Division, Maryland Volunteers was commanded by George H. Steuart (militia general)\". Specifically, the documents state:\n\n1. \"From 1841 to 1861 the senior militia general was George H. Steuart, commander of the First Light Division.\"\n2. \"In 1833 a number of Baltimore regiments were formed into a brigade, and Steuart was promoted from colonel to brigadier general.\"\n\nThese details confirm that George H. Steuart held the position of commander for the First Light Division, Maryland Volunteer Militia, supporting the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}